What does the future hold for me?  Should I
be worried, and what's
the best advice for saying, "Don't
get overwhelmed by innovation"?
First of all, to avoid being overwhelmed,
you need to start playing or using
this technology immediately.  I think
maybe even 6 months ago there were still
many detractors of forums.  Now, if
I remember correctly, I think it was exactly in December that
Lino Stor said for the first time
in my life that I wrote Software with him and he
wrote it better than I had
done.  He clearly wasn't
writing Linox kernel code, but
he realized it saved him a lot of time
and is a useful technology.
That in my opinion was Pivot al
Moment.  I agree because Linus is
the idol of quitters who hated
coding.  And at that point there was
this mindset shift.  Everyone has decided
to embrace this new technology.
If you're a
college student or have this
career in mind, spend as much time as you can
learning how to use these tools
optimally.  The other piece of advice I
give is to perhaps be even more
open-minded than before when it comes to
the job offers you're
receiving.  I remember maybe when
I was 20, trying to
figure out what my first steps after university would be.
I had a general idea
of ​​the things I was pretty
good at and the things I would never be
good at.  For example, I've never
been a good frontend developer, I don't
know much about design, there are some things I've
never spent too many hours
of my life trying to study.
Now it won't work like that anymore.  In my opinion, it's best to
optimize your work with a team of
people you feel comfortable with, who are
working on a product you like,
and who are passionate about the
mission, the startup, the company
you're joining, and prepare yourself to
learn as much as possible, as
quickly as possible.  It still makes sense
to study.  I'm not telling people not to
go to university, it's a waste of
time, but it needs to be approached
differently than if I
hadn't gone.